<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drawing on Chris Short</title>
    <link>/tags/drawing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drawing on Chris Short</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 14:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/drawing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspective</title>
      <link>/post/perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/perspective/</guid>
      <description>I like to remind everyone this time of year that, unless they have people&amp;rsquo;s lives in their hands, you have to keep things in perspective.

Chances are you&amp;rsquo;re in a terminal on a laptop on planet earth which is but one watery orb circling a star as it hurtles through the Milky Way which is but one of many galaxies moving across the universe. Try not to take things too seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing: DNS is Awesome</title>
      <link>/post/drawing-dns-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/drawing-dns-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>There are so many cool things about DNS one drawing is not going to do it justice. Please let this drawing serve as an inspiration to learn more about DNS.
DNS is awesome because it allows you to have a full blown CDN for next to nothing. All you have to do is create a CNAME that points to Amazon S3 or Google Storage.
If you are interested in monitoring your DNS records I would highly recommend dnsspy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Buffer using IFTTT</title>
      <link>/post/diy-buffer-using-ifttt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/diy-buffer-using-ifttt/</guid>
      <description>Buffer is a great tool for scheduling and posting content to social media. But, it costs money to do any sort of real sharing. I prefer to share more content from others than I do my own. Paying money to share other people&amp;rsquo;s content is fine but not for me. I came up with an alternative that might be useful to others so here it is:
You will need a place to save links like Pocket (Instapaper or any other comparable service that interfaces with IFTTT works).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTP/2 Primer</title>
      <link>/post/http2-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/http2-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hypertext Transport Protocol v2 (HTTP/2) is here and is being implemented at an ever quickening pace. HTTP/2 is going to speed up the web and enable new capabilities. There is a lot that stays the same but there are some significant changes coming. In educating myself I decided to illustrate some of the changes in HTTP/2:
The first thing to keep in mind is the primary reason for HTTP/2 even being a protocol is to improve performance (and not necessarily security).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing: OSI Model</title>
      <link>/post/osi-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/osi-model/</guid>
      <description>The Open Systems Interconnection model (OSI model) defines a concept where every function of a computing system resides at one of its seven levels. When people say, &amp;ldquo;Layer 3 routing&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;L7 load balancing&amp;rdquo; they are referring to the OSI Model.
It is an incredibly handy tool for troubleshooting as it reminds you to check the system at each layer. The official documentation on the OSI Model can be found on the ISO site (yes, that&amp;rsquo;s confusing).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP Memory Directives Relationship</title>
      <link>/post/php-memory-relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/php-memory-relationships/</guid>
      <description>I recently had to templatize PHP configurations using Ansible and Jinja2. I had to do some research to ensure that the memory directives that were being defined were actually valid. The three directives I was tinkering with were:
 memory_limit upload_max_filesize post_max_size  These three directives values&amp;rsquo; are actually tied together. memory_limit is the max amount of memory that a script can consume. upload_max_filesize defines the largest size a file upload can be.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>