<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Center For Purposeful Living on Chris Short</title>
    <link>/tags/center-for-purposeful-living/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Center For Purposeful Living on Chris Short</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 09:18:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/center-for-purposeful-living/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Center for Purposeful Living</title>
      <link>/center-for-purposeful-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 09:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/center-for-purposeful-living/</guid>
      <description>As many already know, there is a cult in Winston-Salem, North Carolina that has been deceiving people and ruining families for dozens of years called the Center for Purposeful Living. This cult was formerly known as Human Service Alliance and, at one point, University for Human Goodness.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The Center for Purposeful Living has done irreparable harm to several families and numerous people across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Center for Purposeful Living Recruit Saved</title>
      <link>/post/another-center-for-purposeful-living-recruit-saved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/another-center-for-purposeful-living-recruit-saved/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I had an incredibly healthy exchange with a divorced mother who had toured the Center for Purposeful Living and decided it might be worth her time. She even enlisted to join the Center for Purposeful Living after her tour.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  However, for whatever reason Joanna White, my estranged biological mother, from the Center for Purposeful Living advised this person to see the thread over at FACTNet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Center for Purposeful Living by John David Short</title>
      <link>/post/a-brief-history-of-center-for-purposeful-living-by-john-david-short-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2005 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-brief-history-of-center-for-purposeful-living-by-john-david-short-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week my brother, John David Short, and I had a conversation about all the statements and articles that have been written about the Center for Purposeful Living (formally known as Human Service Alliance). In that conversation he told me that he’d be willing to write about Human Service Alliance (what it was aptly named while he and I were involved in it). He sent me a very well written article that is just too good not to add to the mountain of information forming in regards to the Center for Purposeful Living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Teachings of Derwyn Lackey</title>
      <link>/post/the-teachings-of-derwyn-lackey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2005 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-teachings-of-derwyn-lackey/</guid>
      <description>I’ve told you about the cult known as the Center for Purposeful Living, another person has shared their experiences with the Center for Purposeful Living, and now another individual has come out denouncing the Center for Purposeful Living which is also known as Human Service Alliance.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The following was originally posted on the FACTNet thread dedicated to Human Service Alliance and the Center for Purposeful Living by someone referring to themselves as marcusrevelus and is being republished here because it is so incredibly powerful and remarkably true:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Center for Purposeful Living is a Cult: Don’t Take My Word For It</title>
      <link>/post/the-center-for-purposeful-living-is-a-cult-dont-take-my-word-for-it-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2005 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-center-for-purposeful-living-is-a-cult-dont-take-my-word-for-it-2/</guid>
      <description>It’s obvious I’m not the only one that believes Human Service Alliance, University for Human Goodness, Center for Purposeful Living, or whatever they are calling themselves this week is a cult. That fact is apparent to many not engulfed in the organization including those that have had some limited experience with the cult. A few nights ago I had an exchange of e-mails with someone who wishes to remain anonymous (so for the sake of this article we’ll call them Quincy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cult that is Human Service Alliance and the Center for Purposeful Living</title>
      <link>/post/the-cult-that-is-human-service-alliance-and-the-center-for-purposeful-living-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2005 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-cult-that-is-human-service-alliance-and-the-center-for-purposeful-living-2/</guid>
      <description>Allow me to take a moment to inform you about a dark part of my past that I have kept from quite a few people; while I was a child I was an unwilling member of a cult known then as Human Service Alliance and after quite a few name changes (to include the University for Human Goodness) it is now known as the Center for Purposeful Living. I was young and when you’re in an environment like that you don’t know any better regardless of your age.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>