<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mac Os X on Chris Short</title>
    <link>https://chrisshort.net/tags/mac-os-x/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mac Os X on Chris Short</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 22:24:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chrisshort.net/tags/mac-os-x/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Remote Desktop for Mac</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/microsoft-remote-desktop-for-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 22:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/microsoft-remote-desktop-for-mac/</guid>
      <description>On June 1, 2016, Microsoft released an update to it&amp;rsquo;s Remote Desktop client for Mac OS X via the Mac App Store. The update to version 8.0.32 broke some functionality for people. The most commonly reported error I have seen is &amp;ldquo;Connection reset to peer&amp;rdquo; before authentication.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  Sadly, unless you have a Time Machine backup to grab the old version from you are likely going to have to find an alternative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Mac OS X Setup Guide</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/my-mac-os-x-setup-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 19:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/my-mac-os-x-setup-guide/</guid>
      <description>I happen to be someone that finds themselves setting up new systems for myself often. I have to remind myself there are tools that I need installed before the scenario in which I need to use them (on an airplane, during a crisis, etc.). I use a Mac so this list of software and setup is going to be very Mac OS X centric.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNU sed on Mac OS X</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/gnu-sed-on-mac-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/gnu-sed-on-mac-os-x/</guid>
      <description>Like a lot of systems folks I use sed, a lot. It is probably an unhealthy amount of sed use but so be it. I operate on a lot of Linux servers but my desktop environment of choice is Mac OS X which means BSD tools (not the Linux-y GNU tools).
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The differences are relatively subtle between BSD sed and GNU sed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangible Intangibles: Questions to Ask While Being Interviewed</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/tangible-intangibles-questions-to-ask-while-being-interviewed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/tangible-intangibles-questions-to-ask-while-being-interviewed/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago a co-worker and I were discussing some things we really enjoyed about our work environment. It reminded me of a few key questions I ask (or things that I look for) during an interview that typically indicate whether or not a job is going to be a good fit or not.
What do you use for e-mail?
It is a simple question but the answer tells you a lot about a company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yubikey 4 Nano Demands Use of yubiswitch</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/yubikey-4-nano-demands-use-of-yubiswitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/yubikey-4-nano-demands-use-of-yubiswitch/</guid>
      <description>As more and more security policies demand the use of multi-factor authentication the number of times a day you use a multi-factor token will increase. Hopefully that number will not increase to a level that throws the balance of security and convenience towards the annoyingly secure side of the scale. But, if that ever does happen hopefully you can use an Yubikey as your token.
   (adsbygoogle = window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disabling Mac OS X El Capitan System Integrity Protection</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/disabling-mac-os-x-el-capitan-system-integrity-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 17:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/disabling-mac-os-x-el-capitan-system-integrity-protection/</guid>
      <description>Apple has introduced a new security feature in Mac OS X El Capitan (10.11) called System Integrity Protection (sometimes referred to as rootless).
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  What is System Integrity Protection? According to Apple&amp;rsquo;s documentation:
 A new security policy that applies to every running process, including privileged code and code that runs out of the sandbox. The policy extends additional protections to components on disk and at run-time, only allowing system binaries to be modified by the system installer and software updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X El Capitan and Junos Pulse</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/mac-os-x-el-capitan-and-junos-pulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 20:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/mac-os-x-el-capitan-and-junos-pulse/</guid>
      <description>I had some Apple Keychain issues after upgrading to Mac OS X El Capitan yesterday. Apple provided a reasonable resolution (blow away the login Apple Keychain and re-create it). As it turns out, my issues weren&amp;rsquo;t limited to just the El Capitan upgrade. The Juniper Networks&amp;rsquo; VPN client, Junos Pulse, has some pretty awful issues.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The behavior went something like this: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X El Capitan: Keychain Issues</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/mac-os-x-el-capitan-keychain-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 20:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/mac-os-x-el-capitan-keychain-issues/</guid>
      <description>I started having some Apple Keychain issues after upgrading to Mac OS X El Capitan. At random, I would be asked to sign back into accounts that I am logged into through Internet Accounts in System Preferences.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  I thought it a minor issue but it became unavoidable though once El Capitan told me it couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my login Apple Keychain after logging in:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>