<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Chris Short</title>
    <link>https://chrisshort.net/categories/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Chris Short</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 13:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chrisshort.net/categories/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina Veterans Oral History Interview Part 1</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/nc-vets-oral-history-interview-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/nc-vets-oral-history-interview-1/</guid>
      <description>As part of a North Carolina State Archives initiative to obtain oral histories of veterans I volunteered to be interviewed for the North Carolina Veterans Oral History Collection. I was interviewed by Matthew Peek, Military Collection Archivist for the North Carolina Department of Natural and Cultural Resources (later referred to as MP).
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The interview was well worth the time it took to coordinate and conduct it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangible Intangibles: Questions to Ask While Being Interviewed</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/tangible-intangibles-questions-to-ask-while-being-interviewed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/tangible-intangibles-questions-to-ask-while-being-interviewed/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago a co-worker and I were discussing some things we really enjoyed about our work environment. It reminded me of a few key questions I ask (or things that I look for) during an interview that typically indicate whether or not a job is going to be a good fit or not.
What do you use for e-mail?
It is a simple question but the answer tells you a lot about a company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Directory Structure</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/linux-directory-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2005 01:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/linux-directory-structure/</guid>
      <description>For more information about the Linux directory structure see the Filesystem Hierarchy Standard (FHS) which is part of the Linux Standard Base (LSB) which is a workgroup of the Free Standards Group.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  / The root directory (not to be concerned with the root account) is similar to a drive letter in Windows (C:\, D:\, etc.) except that in the Linux directory structure there is only one root directory and everything falls under it (including other filesystems and partitions).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Linux - Linux Hopes Dashed</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-linux-hopes-dashed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2003 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-linux-hopes-dashed/</guid>
      <description>This will be the final article in the &amp;ldquo;Moving to Linux&amp;rdquo; series.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The Moving to Linux plan had been going along as it should. My Western Digital 200 GB hard drive arrived and I was ready and waiting with a freshly burned copy of Red Hat 9. All the research I had previously done indicated that there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be any major issues because of all the key components in my computer being compatible with Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Linux - Filesystems</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-filesystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2003 01:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-filesystems/</guid>
      <description>After deciding how my hard disk will be partitioned in Linux, I need to select a filesystem for those partitions. A filesystem is a system for organizing directories and files, generally in terms of how it is implemented in the disk operating system. In layman&amp;rsquo;s terms it is code that tells your operating system how data is stored, organized, and managed on a hard disk drive. Every operating system has a filesystem of some sort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Linux - Partitioning</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-partitioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2003 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-partitioning/</guid>
      <description>After deciding to make the move to Linux, determining that my hardware is compatible with Linux, and after picking a Linux distro it&amp;rsquo;s time to decide how to partition my hard drive.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  Unlike Microsoft Windows where one partition is usually the case, Linux users agree that a few partitions should be made for certain paths that Linux uses. I&amp;rsquo;ve done some research on the Linux Directory Structure and that would be very helpful information to read before continuing if you&amp;rsquo;re not too familiar with Linux already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Linux - Picking a Distribution</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-picking-a-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-picking-a-distribution/</guid>
      <description>After deciding to move to Linux and determining that my hardware is compatible with Linux, it&amp;rsquo;s time to pick a Linux distribution.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  Choosing the right distribution for you is exactly that. You have to choose the right distribution for YOU. There is no one size fits all Linux distro. You have to think about what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for in a Linux distro and essentially rule out the ones that won&amp;rsquo;t fit you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Linux - Hardware Compatibility</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-hardware-compatibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2003 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>chris@chrisshort.net (Chris Short)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/post/moving-to-linux-hardware-compatibility/</guid>
      <description>The first step when preparing for the move to Linux is to make sure that your hardware is compatible. It requires a great deal of research when you get very specific (as I did). For example, I have a Logitech QuickCam Express and I wanted to make sure it would work with the latest Linux kernel. Well initially one would say, &amp;ldquo;Well it&amp;rsquo;s USB 1.1 it should work in Linux, no problem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>